/bin/sh: 11651: inaccessible or not found
/bin/sh: model_run: inaccessible or not found
/bin/sh: leak: inaccessible or not found
/bin/sh: fault: inaccessible or not found
/bin/sh: cppcrash: inaccessible or not found
/bin/sh: jscrash: inaccessible or not found
/bin/sh: appfreeze: inaccessible or not found
/bin/sh: sysfreeze: inaccessible or not found
/bin/sh: dump: inaccessible or not found
Signal 11 (core dumped) 
